http://www.pegasusinfocorp.com/privacy-statement.html

Privacy Statement
In general, you can visit Pegasus InfoCorp's websites without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used, and we will make every effort to ensure that our activities keep within the spirit of this Privacy Policy. This privacy statement explains the data we collect from you and its use. We encourage you to read the complete privacy statement.
Our web server automatically collects your IP address when your visit our site. (Your IP address is your computer's unique address that lets other computers attached to the Internet know where to send data, but does not identify you individually). We use your IP address to help diagnose problems on our server and to compile statistics on site usage. We do not make your IP address available to anyone. When you visit certain areas of the website you may be asked to provide personal information (such as name, organization name, email address) that we need to process your request. In the event that you decline to provide such information, we are unable to process your information request. Still, we invite you to continue to visit the site and take advantage of the wealth of information it offers.
There is nothing special about the information described, and the practice of collecting this data has been generally standardized by virtually every Web Server on the Internet today.
Third Parties:
Pegasus InfoCorp will disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to
conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on Pegasus InfoCorp
Protect and defend the rights or property of Pegasus InfoCorp, or visitors of www.pegasusinfocorp.com.
Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties.
Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.
Antispam policy:
Pegasus InfoCorp recognizes the receipt, transmission or distribution of spam emails (unsolicited bulk emails) as a major concern and has taken reasonable measures, to minimize the transmission and effect of spam emails in its computing environment. All emails received by Pegasus InfoCorp, are subject to spam check. Any email identified as spam will be rejected. With this measure, along with other technical spam reduction measures, Pegasus InfoCorp hopes to minimize the effect of spam emails. Pegasus InfoCorp reserves the right to reject and/or report any suspicious spam emails, to the authorities concerned, for necessary action, from time to time.
To know more about us, our services and solutions, drop us a message
Pvt. Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
